saymedia.com 2019-06-28

# Say Media :: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how we, Say Media, Inc. (“Say Media,” “we” or “us”), collect, store and use information about you when you use or interact with our websites, [www.saymedia.com](https://www.saymedia.com/), [tempest.saymedia.com](https://tempest.saymedia.com/), and other websites and mobile services provided by Say Media (collectively the “Network Websites”) and where we otherwise obtain or collect information about you. This Privacy Policy is effective from May 25, 2018.

#### Contents

  * Summary
  * Our details
  * Information we collect when you visit our website
  * Information we collect when you contact us
  * Information we collect when you interact with our website
  * How we collect or obtain information about you from third parties
  * Disclosure and additional uses of your information
  * How long we retain your information
  * How we secure your information
  * Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area
  * Your rights in relation to your information
  * Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes
  * Sensitive Personal Information
  * Changes to our Privacy Policy
  * Children’s Privacy
  * California Do Not Track Disclosures

#### Summary

This section summarises how we obtain, store and use information about you. It is intended to provide a very general overview only. It is not complete in and of itself and it must be read in conjunction with the corresponding full sections of this Privacy Policy.

  * Data controller: Say Media, Inc. 
  * How we collect or obtain information about you:

  * when you provide it to us (e.g. by contacting us, placing an order on our Network Websites and signing up for any email newsletter),
  * from your use of our website, using cookies and similar technologies, and
  * occasionally, from third parties.

  * Information we collect: name, email address, contact details, payment information (e.g. your credit or debit card details), IP address, information from cookies, information about your computer or device (e.g. device and browser type), and information about how you use our website (e.g. which pages you have viewed, the time when you viewed them and what you clicked on).
  * How we use your information: for administrative and business purposes (particularly to contact you and process orders you place on our website), to improve our business and Network Websites, to fulfill our contractual obligations, to advertise our goods and services, to analyze your use of our website, and in connection with our legal rights and obligations.
  * Disclosure of your information to third parties: only to the extent necessary to run our business, to our service providers, to fulfill any contracts we enter into with you, and where required by law or to enforce our legal rights.
  * Do we sell your information to third parties (other than in the course of a business sale or purchase or similar event): No.
  * How long we retain your information: for no longer than necessary, taking into account any legal obligations we have (e.g. to maintain records for tax purposes), and any other legal basis we have for using your information (e.g. your consent, performance of a contract with you or our legitimate interests as a business). For specific retention periods in relation to certain information which we collect from you, please see the main section below entitled How long we retain your information.
  * How we secure your information: using appropriate technical and organisational measures such as encrypting transfers of data to or from our servers using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, encrypting payments you make on or via our website using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, only granting access to your information where necessary.
  * Use of cookies and similar technologies: we use cookies and similar information-gathering technologies such as web beacons on our Network Websites including essential, functional, analytical and targeting cookies. For more information, please visit our cookies policy here: www.saymedia.com/cookiepolicy
  * Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area: in certain circumstances we transfer your information outside of the European Economic Area, including to the following countries: United States of America. Where we do so, we will ensure appropriate safeguards are in place.
  * Use of automated decision making and profiling: we do not use automated decision making.
  * Your rights in relation to your information

  * to access your information and to receive information about its use
  * to have your information corrected and/or completed
  * to have your information deleted
  * to restrict the use of your information
  * to receive your information in a portable format
  * to object to the use of your information
  * to withdraw your consent to the use of your information
  * to complain to a supervisory authority

  * Sensitive personal information: we do not knowingly or intentionally collect what is commonly referred to as ‘sensitive personal information’. Please do not submit sensitive personal information about you to us. For more information, please see the main section below entitled Sensitive Personal Information.

#### Our details

The data controller in respect of our website is Say Media, Inc. of 442 Post Street, 9th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94101, USA. You can contact the data controller by writing to the above address or sending an email to [legal@saymedia.com](mailto:legal@saymedia.com).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact the data controller.

#### Information we collect when you visit our website

We collect and use information from website visitors in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure and additional uses of your information.

#### Web server log information

We use third party servers to host our Network Websites called Amazon Web Services and Fastly, the privacy policies of which are available here: [aws.amazon.com/privacy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/) and [www.fastly.com/privacy](https://www.fastly.com/privacy). Our website server automatically logs the IP address you use to access our website as well as other information about your visit such as the pages accessed, the date and time of the request, the source of your access to our website (e.g. the website or URL (link) which referred you to our website), and your browser version and operating system.

Our server is located in the United States and, accordingly, your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area (EEA). For further information and information on the safeguards used, please see the section of this privacy policy entitled Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area.

Use of website server log information for IT security purposes

We and our third-party hosting providers collect and store server logs to ensure network and IT security and so that the server and website remain uncompromised. This includes analyzing log files to help identify and prevent unauthorised access to our network, the distribution of malicious code, denial of services attacks and other cyber-attacks, by detecting unusual or suspicious activity.

Unless we are investigating suspicious or potential criminal activity, we do not make, nor do we allow our hosting provider to make, any attempt to identify you from the information collected via server logs.

Use of website server log information to analyse website use and improve our website

We use the information collected by our website server logs to analyze how our website users interact with our website and its features. For example, we analyse the number of visits and unique visitors we receive, the time and date of the visit, the location of the visit, the operating system and browser used and the source that referred the visit to our website.

We use the information gathered from the analysis of this information to improve our website. For example, we use the information gathered to change the information, content and structure of our website and individual pages based according to what users are engaging most with and the duration of time spent on particular pages on our website.

#### Cookies and similar technologies

Cookies are data files which are sent from a website to a browser to record information about users for various purposes.

We use cookies and similar technologies on our website, including essential, functional, analytical and targeting cookies and web beacons. For further information on how we use cookies, please see our cookies policy which is available here: www.saymedia.com/cookiepolicy.

You can reject some or all of the cookies we use on or via our website by changing your browser settings or non-essential cookies by using our cookie control tool, but doing so can impair your ability to use our website or some or all of its features. For further information about cookies, including how to change your browser settings, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or see our cookies policy.

#### Information we collect when you contact us

We collect and use information from individuals who contact us in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure and additional uses of your information.

Email  
When you send an email to the email address displayed on our website we collect your email address and any other information you provide in that email (such as your name, telephone number and the information contained in any signature block in your email).  
Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so.

Transfer and storage of your information  
We use a third-party email provider to store emails you send us. Our third-party email provider is MailChimp located in the USA. Their privacy policy is available here: [mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).  
Emails you send us will be stored outside the European Economic Area on our third-party email provider’s servers in the USA. For further information please see the section of this privacy policy entitled Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area.

Post  
If you contact us by post, we will collect any information you provide to us in any postal communications you send us.  
Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).

#### Information we collect when you interact with our website

We collect and use information from individuals who interact with particular features of our website in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure and additional uses of your information.

E-Newsletter  
When you sign up for our e-newsletter on our website or opt to receive news and offers from us by entering your name and email address and clicking subscribe, we collect your name and e-mail address.

Transfer and storage of your information  
We use a third-party service to send out our e-newsletter and administer our mailing list, MailChimp. Their privacy policy is available here: [mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

Information you submit to subscribe for our e-newsletter will be stored outside the European Economic Area on our third-party mailing list provider’s servers in the USA. For further information about the safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area, see the section of this privacy policy below entitled Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area.

Registering on our website  
When you register and create an account on our website, we collect the following information: Name, E-mail address, IP address, and any other information you provide to us when you complete the registration form.

If you do not provide the mandatory information required by the registration form, you will not be able to register or create an account on our website.

Transfer and storage of your information  
Information you submit to us via the registration form on our website will be stored outside the European Economic Area on our third-party hosting provider’s servers in the USA. Our third-party hosting provider is Amazon Web Services. Their privacy policy is available here: [aws.amazon.com/privacy/](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/).

For further information about the safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area, see the section of this privacy policy below entitled Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area.

#### Information collected or obtained from third parties

This section sets out how we obtain or collect information about you from third parties.

Information received from third parties  
Generally, we do not receive information about you from third parties. The third parties from which we receive information about you will generally include DoubleClick for Publishers, Carbon by Clicksco, Auth0 and Facebook.

It is also possible that third parties with whom we have had no prior contact may provide us with information about you.

Information we obtain from third parties will generally be your name and contact details but will include any additional information about you which they provide to us.

Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where a third party has passed on information about you to us (such as your name and email address) in order for us to provide services to you, we will process your information in order to take steps at your request to enter into a contract with you and perform a contract with you (as the case may be).

Consent: where you have asked that a third party to share information about you with us and the purpose of sharing that information is not related to the performance of a contract or services by us to you, we will process your information on the basis of your consent, which you give by asking the third party in question to pass on your information to us.

Legitimate interests: where a third party has shared information about you with us and you have not consented to the sharing of that information, we will have a legitimate interest in processing that information in certain circumstances.

For example, we would have a legitimate interest in processing your information to perform our obligations under a sub-contract with the third party, where the third party has the main contract with you. Our legitimate interest is the performance of our obligations under our sub-contract.  
Similarly, third parties may pass on information about you to us if you have infringed or potentially infringed any of our legal rights. In this case, we will have a legitimate interest in processing that information to investigate and pursue any such potential infringement.

Where we receive information about you in error  
If we receive information about you from a third party in error and/or we do not have a legal basis for processing that information, we will delete your information.

Information obtained by us from third parties  
In certain circumstances (for example, to verify the information we hold about you or obtain missing information we require to provide you with a service) we will obtain information about you from certain publicly accessible sources, both EU and non-EU, such as media publications, social media, and websites (including your own website if you have one).

Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where you have entered into a contract or requested that we enter into a contract with you, in certain circumstances, we will obtain information about you from public sources in order to enable us to understand your business and provide services to you or services to a sufficient standard.

For example, we would obtain and/or verify your email address from your website or from a directory where you ask us to send you information by email but we do not possess the information or we need to confirm that we have recorded your email address correctly.

Legitimate interests: in certain circumstances, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining information about you from public and private sources. For example, if you have infringed or we suspect that you have infringed any of our legal rights, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining and processing information about you from such sources in order to investigate and pursue any suspected or potential infringement.

#### Disclosure and additional uses of your information

This section sets out the circumstances in which will disclose information about you to third parties and any additional purposes for which we use your information.

Disclosure of your information to service providers  
We use a number of third parties to provide us with services which are necessary to run our business or to assist us with running our business and who process your information for us on our behalf. These include the following:

  * Email provider(s), including MailChimp, Zendesk and SendGrid. Their privacy policies are available here:

  * IT service provider(s), including Auth0, Adobe Typekit, Stripe, Disqus, Embed.ly, Google DoubleClick for Publishers, and Google Analytics. Their privacy policy is available here:

  * Hosting provider(s), including Amazon Web Services, Fastly, Cloudinary and JW Player. Their privacy policy is available here:[ ](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/)

Your information will be shared with these service providers where necessary to provide you with the service you have requested, whether that is accessing our website or ordering goods and services from us.

Legitimate interest relied on: where we share your information with these third parties in a context other than where is necessary to perform a contract (or take steps at your request to do so), we will share your information with such third parties in order to allow us to run and manage our business efficiently.

Reason why necessary to perform a contract: we may need to share information with our service providers to enable us to perform our obligations under that contract or to take the steps you have requested before we enter into a contract with you.

Disclosure of your information to other third parties  
We disclose your information to other third parties in specific circumstances, as set out below.

Providing information to third parties such as Google Inc. Google collects information through our use of Google Analytics on our website. Google uses this information, including IP addresses and information from cookies, for a number of purposes, such as improving its Google Analytics service. Information is shared with Google on an aggregated and anonymized basis. To find out more about what information Google collects, how it uses this information and how to control the information sent to Google, please see the following page: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

You can opt out of Google Analytics by installing the browser plugin here: [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Transfer and storage of your information  
Information collected by Google Analytics is stored outside the European Economic Area on Google’s servers in the United States of America.

For further information about the safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the European Economic Area, see the section of this privacy policy below entitled Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area.

Sharing your information with third parties, which are either related to or associated with the running of our business, where it is necessary for us to do so. These third parties include our advisors, independent contractors, and insurers. Further information on each of these third parties is set out below.

Advisors  
Occasionally, we obtain advice from advisors, such as accountants and lawyers. We will share your information with these third parties only where it is necessary to enable these third parties to be able to provide us with the relevant advice.

Independent contractors  
Occasionally, we use independent contractors in our business. Your information will be shared with independent contractors only where it is necessary for them to perform the function we have hired them to perform in relation to our business.

Insurers  
We will share your information with our insurers where it is necessary to do so, for example in relation to a claim or potential claim we receive or make or under our general disclosure obligations under our insurance contract with them.

Sharing your information with a prospective or actual purchaser or seller in the context of a business or asset sale or acquisition by us, a merger or similar business combination event, whether actual or potential.

Disclosure and use of your information for legal reasons  
Indicating possible criminal acts or threats to public security to a competent authority  
If we suspect that criminal or potential criminal conduct has occurred, we will in certain circumstances need to contact an appropriate authority, such as the police. This could be the case, for instance, if we suspect that fraud or a cyber-crime has been committed or if we receive threats or malicious communications towards us or third parties.

We will generally only need to process your information for this purpose if you were involved or affected by such an incident in some way.

In connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement our legal rights  
We will use your information in connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement of our legal rights, including, for example, sharing information with debt collection agencies if you do not pay amounts owed to us when you are contractually obliged to do so. Our legal rights may be contractual (where we have entered into a contract with you) or non-contractual (such as legal rights that we have under copyright law or tort law).

In connection with a legal or potential legal dispute or proceedings  
We may need to use your information if we are involved in a dispute with you or a third party for example, either to resolve the dispute or as part of any mediation, arbitration or court resolution or similar process.

For ongoing compliance with laws, regulations and other legal requirements  
We will use and process your information in order to comply with legal obligations to which we are subject. For example, we may need to disclose your information pursuant to a court order or subpoena if we receive one.

#### How long we retain your information

This section sets out how long we retain your information. We have set out specific retention periods where possible. Where that has not been possible, we have set out the criteria we use to determine the retention period.

Retention periods  
Server log information: we retain information on our server logs for 14 months.

Order information: when you place an order for goods and services, we retain that information for six years following the end of the financial year in which you placed your order, in accordance with our legal obligation to keep records for tax purposes.

Correspondence and enquiries: when you make an enquiry or correspond with us for any reason, whether by email or via our contact form, we will retain your information for as long as it takes to respond to and resolve your enquiry, and for 36 further month(s), after which point we will delete your information.

E-Newsletter: we retain the information you used to sign up for our e-newsletter for as long as you remain subscribed (i.e. you do not unsubscribe) or if we decide to cancel our e-newsletter service, whichever comes earlier.

Criteria for determining retention periods  
In any other circumstances, we will retain your information for no longer than necessary, taking into account the following:

  * the purpose(s) and use of your information both now and in the future (such as whether it is necessary to continue to store that information in order to continue to perform our obligations under a contract with you or to contact you in the future);
  * whether we have any legal obligation to continue to process your information (such as any record-keeping obligations imposed by relevant law or regulation);
  * whether we have any legal basis to continue to process your information (such as your consent);
  * how valuable your information is (both now and in the future);
  * any relevant agreed industry practices on how long information should be retained;
  * the levels of risk, cost and liability involved with us continuing to hold the information;
  * how hard it is to ensure that the information can be kept up to date and accurate; and
  * any relevant surrounding circumstances (such as the nature and status of our relationship with you).

#### How we secure your information

We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to secure your information and to protect it against unauthorised or unlawful use and accidental loss or destruction, including:

  * only sharing and providing access to your information to the minimum extent necessary, subject to confidentiality restrictions where appropriate, and on an anonymized basis wherever possible;
  * verifying the identity of any individual who requests access to information prior to granting them access to information; and,
  * using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt any information you submit to us via any forms on our website and any payment transactions you make on or via our website.

Transmission of information to us by email  
Transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure, and if you submit any information to us over the internet (whether by email, via our website or any other means), you do so entirely at your own risk.  
We cannot be responsible for any costs, expenses, loss of profits, harm to reputation, damages, liabilities or any other form of loss or damage suffered by you as a result of your decision to transmit information to us by such means.

#### GDPR and Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area

If you are located in the European Economic Area, your information will be transferred and stored outside the United States in the circumstances set out below. We will also transfer your information outside the EEA or to an international organization in order to comply with legal obligations to which we are subject (compliance with a court order, for example). Where we are required to do so, we will ensure appropriate safeguards and protections are in place.

Server log information  
Information collected when you visit our website is transferred outside of the EEA and stored on the servers of our third-party hosting company, Amazon Web Services. You can access their privacy policy here: [aws.amazon.com/privacy/](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/).

Country of storage: The relevant servers which collect information in relation to the Network Websites are located in the United States. This country is not subject to an adequacy decision by the European Commission.

Safeguard(s) used: our third-party hosting provider has self-certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.

Email  
Information you submit to us by email is transferred outside the EEA and stored on our third-party email provider’s servers. Our third-party email provider is: MailChimp. You can access their privacy policy here: [mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

Country of storage: The relevant servers which collect information in relation to the Network Websites are located in the United States. This country is not subject to an adequacy decision by the European Commission.

Safeguard(s) used: our third-party email provider has self-certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.

Legal Basis  
Our legal basis for collection and processing of personal data is as follows:

  * consent explicitly given by you for the purpose requested;
  * legal compliance and/or vital interest, as mandated by a valid and binding request from an applicable government entity with proper jurisdiction;
  * contractual performance, for example with respect to activities initiated by you on the website;
  * legitimate interests pursued by us (or third parties we use) include specific activities initiated by you on the service and/or fraud/anti-spam protection, security, authentication, load-balancing, and other fundamental provisioning and protections for both registered and unregistered users of the website.

#### Your rights in relation to your information

Subject to certain limitations on certain rights, you have the following rights in relation to your information, which you can exercise by writing to Say Media Inc., 442 Post Street, 9th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94102 or sending an email to legal@saymedia.com:

  * to request access to your information and information related to our use and processing of your information;
  * to request the correction or deletion of your information;
  * to request that we restrict our use of your information;
  * to receive information which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format (e.g. a CSV file) and the right to have that information transferred to another data controller (including a third-party data controller);
  * to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes (for further information, see the section below entitled Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes); and
  * to withdraw your consent to our use of your information at any time where we rely on your consent to use or process that information. Please note that if you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the lawfulness of our use and processing of your information on the basis of your consent before the point in time when you withdraw your consent.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, in accordance with Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation. You can also find out further information about your rights, as well as information on any limitations which apply to those rights, by reading the underlying legislation contained in Articles 12 to 22 and 34 of the General Data Protection Regulation, which is available here: [ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdf](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdf).

Further information on your rights in relation to your personal data as an individual  
The above rights are provided in summary form only and certain limitations apply to many of these rights. For further information about your rights in relation to your information, including any limitations which apply, please visit the following pages on the ICO’s website:

  * [ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/); and
  * [ico.org.uk/for-the-public/is-my-information-being-handled-correctly/](https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/is-my-information-being-handled-correctly/)

You can also find out further information about your rights, as well as information on any limitations which apply to those rights, by reading the underlying legislation contained in Articles 12 to 22 and 34 of the General Data Protection Regulation, which is available here: [ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdf](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdf)

Verifying your identity where you request access to your information  
Where you request access to your information, we are required by law to use all reasonable measures to verify your identity before doing so.

These measures are designed to protect your information and to reduce the risk of identity fraud, identity theft or general unauthorised access to your information.

How we verify your identity  
Where we possess appropriate information about you on file, we will attempt to verify your identity using that information.

If it is not possible to identity you from such information, or if we have insufficient information about you, we may require original or certified copies of certain documentation in order to be able to verify your identity before we are able to provide you with access to your information.

We will be able to confirm the precise information we require to verify your identity in your specific circumstances if and when you make such a request.

#### Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes

You have the following rights in relation to your information, which you may exercise in the same way as you may exercise by writing to Say Media Inc., 442 Post Street, 9th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94102 or sending an email to [legal@saymedia.com](mailto:legal@saymedia.com):

  * to object to us using or processing your information where we use or process it in order to carry out a task in the public interest or for our legitimate interests, including ‘profiling’ (i.e. analysing or predicting your behaviour based on your information) based on any of these purposes; and
  * to object to us using or processing your information for direct marketing purposes (including any profiling we engage in that is related to such direct marketing).

You may also exercise your right to object to us using or processing your information for direct marketing purposes by:

  * clicking the unsubscribe link contained at the bottom of any marketing email we send to you and following the instructions which appear in your browser following your clicking on that link; or
  * sending an email to [legal@saymedia.com](mailto:legal@saymedia.com), asking that we stop sending you marketing communications or by including the words “OPT OUT”.

You can also opt-out of receiving cookies from third-party data providers in the United States by following the instructions at: [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) and [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), in Canada by following the instructions at: [youradchoices.ca/choices](http://youradchoices.ca/choices), and in the EU at: [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Also, because your choices are not associated with you as a particular individual, if you change computers, web browsers or cookie settings, you will need to re-implement your preferences as described above.

For more information on how to object to our use of information collected from cookies and similar technologies, please see the section entitled How to accept or reject cookies in our cookies policy, which is available here: www.saymedia.com/cookiepolicy.

#### Sensitive Personal Information

‘Sensitive personal information’ is information about an individual that reveals their racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic information, biometric information for the purpose of uniquely identifying an individual, information concerning health or information concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation.

We do not knowingly or intentionally collect sensitive personal information from individuals, and you must not submit sensitive personal information to us.

If, however, you inadvertently or intentionally transmit sensitive personal information to us, you will be considered to have explicitly consented to us processing that sensitive personal information under Article 9(2)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation. We will use and process your sensitive personal information for the purposes of deleting it.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We update and amend our Privacy Policy from time to time.

Minor changes to our Privacy Policy  
Where we make minor changes to our Privacy Policy, we will update our Privacy Policy with a new effective date stated at the beginning of it. Our processing of your information will be governed by the practices set out in that new version of the Privacy Policy from its effective date onwards.

Major changes to our Privacy Policy or the purposes for which we process your information  
Where we make major changes to our Privacy Policy or intend to use your information for a new purpose or a different purpose than the purposes for which we originally collected it, we will notify you by email (where possible) or by posting a notice on our website.

We will provide you with the information about the change in question and the purpose and any other relevant information before we use your information for that new purpose.  
Wherever required, we will obtain your prior consent before using your information for a purpose that is different from the purposes for which we originally collected it.

#### Children’s Privacy

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying regulations protect the privacy of children using the internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect information from persons under the age of 18. The website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from persons under the age of 18.

It is possible that we could receive information pertaining to persons under the age of 18 by the fraud or deception of a third party. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will, where required by law to do so, immediately obtain the appropriate parental consent to use that information or, if we are unable to obtain such parental consent, we will delete the information from our servers. If you would like to notify us of our receipt of information about persons under the age of 18, please do so by sending an email to legal@saymedia.com.

#### California Do Not Track Disclosures

“Do Not Track” is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on a Do Not Track signal in their browser, the browser sends a message to websites requesting that they do not track the user. For information about Do Not Track, please visit [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/)

At this time, we do not respond to Do Not Track browser settings or signals. In addition, we use other technology that is standard to the internet, such as pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies, to track visitors to the website. Those tools may be used by us and by third-parties to collect information about you and your internet activity, even if you have turned on the Do Not Track signal. For information on how to opt out from tracking technologies used on our website, see our cookies policy which is available here: www.saymedia.com/cookiepolicy.

Copyright, credit and logo  
This Privacy Policy is based on a General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/769) (GDPR) compliant template provided by GDPR Privacy Policy. For further information, please visit [gdprprivacypolicy.org](https://gdprprivacypolicy.org/)

The copyright in this Privacy Policy is either owned by, or licensed to, us and is protected by copyright laws around the world and copyright protection software. All intellectual property rights in this document are reserved.
